What's my favourite food
我最喜欢的食物是什么
Before this is gold to me
在我之前这是芒果
I've done this before I just
我已经做到了
Go home
回家
I'm going to be dramatic and I'm trying to get this I don't even know
我会变得充满戏剧性，我正在努力做到这一点，我甚至不知道
I'm bringing it
我拿来
When I go with my 50%
当我和我的50％
Perfect like a surgeon
像外科医生一样完美
I want to just
我只想
Something in the middle of finding stuff
寻找东西中间的东西
How do you get the
你如何得到
After pill
药后
See if I can do anything with you
看看我能对你做什么
God that's what doesn't work
上帝那是行不通的
Going to be a Snow Day
下雪天
It's alright that I'm going
我要走了
Since the mango massacre
自芒果大屠杀以来
Somatotype
体型
Write the sentence after the side
边记
No just like stack it up
不只是像堆叠
And just make
然后做
Is nice little strips
是不错的小条
Put it in space
放在太空
Ironmongers in West rips life-size bites
西部的铁贩子像人一样撕咬
It feels delicious
感觉很好吃
There's an old saying in Brazil that when you know how to cut a mango
You're ready to marry also I'll show you a little trick with mango
你准备结婚了，我会给你看芒果的小技巧
Recorded doing a porcupine
记录做豪猪
我的祖母是妹妹吗
Is my grandmother a sister do
我想带回来
I want to bring a back
这样的芒果
Mango like this
新喜剧
New comedies
我正在看的芒果将在我所属于的某个地方，所以它将成为使用电流前的指标
What I'm looking at the mango there are going to be somewhere I Belong right so that's gonna be the indicator before using current
前往皮特的路线我想去面对，所以窄边就这样面对我
Directions to Pitt is going I want to face it's so the Narrow side is facing me this way
这样一来，我就可以轻松摔倒，因为凹坑相当宽
And that way I can come down the side without hurting a bit because the pit comes fairly wide
如果您想要一个不错的口味，然后轻轻地打分，就可以采取行动，然后我们可以将其完全翻转
Actions if you want a nice taste nice and gently score and then we can actually turn it inside out
这样，碰到并删除所有那些大块的东西，我们当然也可以做切片机
Like this and come across and remove all those huge pieces certainly we could do slicers as well
使用相同的通用技术
Using the same general technique
只是滑动
Just sliding
沿皮肤水平
Horizontally along the skin
告诉我尺寸
Tell me the sizes
所以我们有我的立场
So we have si stand
下一个
Next
两种不同的版本
Two different versions
好胃口
Bon appetit
我们只是
We're just
你得试试
You have to try